Nevada Folklife Archive
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Photographs
  - Subseries 1: Slides, 8,390 still images (.jpg); 8,390 still images (.tif); 14,257 still images (.jpg); 14,257 still images (.tif)
    - Master artist Vinton Hawley and apprentice Lesley Williams, final site visit for FY2005 Master Apprenticeship grant in Paiute and Washoe willow basketry including winnowing tray and cradleboard, July 23, 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-009; Anne F. Hatch; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)
    - Various activities at the Basque Festival, Reno, October 19, 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-010- S-2005-011; Anne F. Hatch; 25 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)
    - Master artist FY2005 Kulvadee Sompong and apprentices Supatra Chemprachum and son. Thai fruit and vegetable carving class at the Thai Buddhist Temple, January 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-012; Dean Burton; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)
    - Apprenticeship site visit with Iola Byers, master cradleboard maker and daughter Mildred Brigham, apprentice, at Iola's home, December 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-013; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)
    - Site visit with master artist Martha Luevanos and apprentice Gerardo Luevanos (her son) to document apprentice project in Mexican Folkloric dance. Also, Life in Death Festival at Winchester Cultural Center, October 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-014; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 10 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)
    - Texture and Weave of Traditional Art exhibition publicity photographs, March 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-015; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)
    - Site visit with master artist Elaine Smokey and apprentice Hanna Maria Smokey, shown at the Fallon Paiute-Shoshone reservation holding Paiute horsehair baskets they have made, December 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-016; 17 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)
    - Site visit with master artist Andy Allen and apprentice Jenny Dick, at the Fallon Paiute-Shoshone reservation's Cultural Day gathering. Also photos of Melba and Katrina Rakow, Elaine Smokey, Deborah Stevenson, Rosemary Rogers-deSoto, Leah Brady, October 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-017; 37 color slides (35mm) (Box 115)
    - Site visit with master artist Joanne Martinez, showing her bracken fern and Washoe willow baskets, March 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-018; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 115)
  - Subseries 2: Negatives, 620 still images (.jpg); 620 still images (.tif)
    Scope and content: Black-and-white negatives of events, art, performances, vernacular architecture, and occupational folklife. Negatives also document the Folklife Apprenticeship Program and various folklife festivals across Nevada.
    Arrangement: This subseries is arranged by the original Item ID number provided by the donor. Negatives are described in groupings based on documentation provided by the donor. In some cases, negatives within a grouping are described at the item level. For further item level description of negatives see Photo Logs.
    - Joan Glass trapping coyote, November 1985, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-001 - P-1986-004; Blanton Owen; 93 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Joan Glass trapping coyote; Sheepherding camp, November 1985, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-005; Blanton Owen; 19 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Alana Charles site visit, November 1985, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-006; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Katie Frazier site visit, December 1985, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-007 - P-1986-008; Blanton Owen; 44 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Harvey Berg site visit, January 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-009; Blanton Owen; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Fire in Virginia City, January 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-010; Blanton Owen; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Doyle Davis site visit (1-14); Spider Teller site visit (15-25), January 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-013; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Spider Teller site visit, January 29, 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-014; Blanton Owen; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Spider Teller site visit (1-11); Martha Dick site visit (12-24), January 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-015; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Martha Dick site visit (1-8); Katie Frazier site visit (9-14); Vernacular architecture (15-24), January 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-016; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular architecture (1-6); Downtown Las Vegas (7-23); Vernacular architecture (24-25), February 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-017; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular Architecture (0-9); Spider Teller site visit (10-12); Mark Dahl site visit (13-23), February 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-019; Blanton Owen; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Mark Dahl site visit (0-13); Stake Ranch site visit (14-19), February 26, 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-020; Blanton Owen; 20 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular architecture -Railroad tie buildings, March 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-021 - P-1986-023; Andrea Graham; 72 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Adam Nordwall site visit, April 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-024; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Adam Nordwall site visit; Native American drumming and singing, April 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-025; Blanton Owen; 21 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Randy and Rosemary Stowell making horsehair rope. Cordano Ranch is Stowell's, May 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-026; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Cordano Ranch leased by Randy Stowell, May 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-027; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Randy Stowell site visit, May 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-028; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Wyoming State Fiddlers Contest, Shoshone, Wyoming, May 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-029; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular architecture and folk art at Walker River Reservation, Schurz (1-14); at Hawthorne (15-21); at Luning (22-24), June 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-030; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Ernie Fanning, Reno (1-6); Folk Art, Reno (7-14); Long Branch Saloon, Luning (15-18), June 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-031; Blanton Owen; 18 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Austin, Gridley Days, June 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-032; Andrea Graham; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Austin, Gridley Days; Vernacular architecture, June 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-033; Andrea Graham; 22 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Austin Fiddle Contest, June 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-034 - P-1986-035; Andrea Graham; 50 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Jensen Historical Farm, Logan, Utah; Larry Schutte site visit, June 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-036; Blanton Owen; 22 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Cheryl Miglioretti at computer in office; Vernacular architecture, July 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-037; Andrea Graham; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular architecture, July 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-038 - P-1986-039; Andrea Graham; 50 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Railroad tie buildings in Lamoille (1-3); in Elko (4-10); at Bear Ranch east of Elko (11-24), July 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-040; Andrea Graham; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Railroad tie buildings at Bear Ranch, east of Elko (0-11); Bernardo Yanci, Basque music (12-17); Railroad tie house in Elko (18-20); log house in Palisade (21-24), July 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-041; Andrea Graham; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Railroad tie buildings, July 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-042 - P-1986-044; Andrea Graham; 46 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Railroad tie church (0-3); State Fair food (4-24), August 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-045; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - State Fair food and crafts, August 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-046; Blanton Owen; 36 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Photos for radio show brochure; Al Ramirez (16-35), August 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-047 - P-1986-048; Blanton Owen; 53 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Tom Martinet (0-20); Stan Forrest (21-35), August 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-049; David Brown; 35 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Pioche scenics (2-13). Reno Air Races (14-25), September 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-050; Blanton Owen; 37 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Reno Air Races, September 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-051 - P-1986-057; Blanton Owen; 190 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Buildings on Stowell's Pie Creek camp (4-13); Home Means Nevada brochure (14-18), October 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-058; Blanton Owen; 20 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Railroad tie architecture (0-10); Virginia City architecture (11-23), September 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-059; Andrea Graham; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Barbara Hall site visit (0-7); Richard Smith site visit (9-20), November 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-060; Blanton Owen; 20 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular architecture, December 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-061; Blanton Owen; 14 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Thunder Mountain, 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1986-062; Blanton Owen; 36 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - New Years celebration (1-5); Vernacular architecture, January 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-001; Blanton Owen; 21 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Brenda Butner TV interview (1-5); Vernacular architecture on Yomba Reservation (6-19); Lincoln County ranch views (18-24), January 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-002; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular architecture in Lincoln County (0-3); in Nye County (5-13); in Ione (14-25), January 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-003; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular architecture in Ione (1-25), January 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-004; Andrea Graham; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular architecture in Reese River Valley (1); on Callahan Ranch in Grass Valley (2-13); and on Grass Valley Ranch (14-25), January 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-005; Andrea Graham; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular architecture (1-25), January 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-006; Andrea Graham; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Poetry gathering - Nevada session. Connie Satterthwaite, Blanton Owen, Jack Walther, Ernie Fanning, Brian Morris, Barbara Hall, Richard Smith, January 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-007; Andrea Graham; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Ranchlands along Meadow Valley Wash, February 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-008; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Lincoln County ghost town, Bristol (1-14); Brad Guyman at sheep camp twelve miles west of Panaca (15-24), February 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-009; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Brad Guyman at sheep camp twelve miles west of Panaca (1-14); Vernacular architecture in Pioche (17-21); aerials of sheep camp (2-6 extra strip), March 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-010; Blanton Owen; 26 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Ranch rodeo, April 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-011; Andrea Graham; 13 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Ranch rodeo with Cassie Funkhouser, Dean Tobias, Randy Stowell, Randy Everett, Lum Hooper, April 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-012; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Ranch rodeo at Stowells' Currie Ranch, with Cassie Funkhouser, Dean Tobias, Randy Stowell, Randy Everett, Lum Hooper, April 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-013; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Stowell's Currie Ranch, April 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-014; Blanton Owen; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Delmue Ranch site visit, McBride family, May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-015; Blanton Owen; 17 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Delmue Ranch site visit, large barn exterior, interior and surroundings, May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-016; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Delmue Ranch site visit (1-7); Panaca (8-17); Round Mountain Mine and town (19-22), May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-017; Blanton Owen; 22 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Delmue Ranch site visit, May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-018 - P-1987-019; Blanton Owen; 50 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Vernacular architecture in Panaca (1-20) including detail of adobe house (6-17); Lester Lee and Debbie Nolan (21-24), May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-020; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Delmue Ranch aerials (1-8); Ballow's Ranch (10-24), May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-021; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Lester Lee interviewed by Michael Luster, Debbie Nolan (1-4); Caliente Homecoming Memorial Days (5-17); Hansen/McBride house in Panaca (18-24), May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-022; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Panaca site visit, May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-023 - P-1987-024; Blanton Owen; 49 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Ballow ranch site visit, May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-025; Blanton Owen; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Hansen/McBride house (3-13); and Grayce Hansen McBride (14-24), May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-026; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Glaser site visit; Halleck site visit (1-11); Barton Ranch, Ryndon Nevada (10-15); Veterans Day Parade in Virginia City (17-21), November 1986, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-028; Andrea Graham; 21 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 6)
    - Copies of photos of Delmue Family photos, June 13, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-101; Michael Luster; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - [Delmue Ranch], June 13, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-102; Michael Luster; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Delmue Ranch (1-14); Condor Canyon (15-21), June 13, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-103; Debbie Nolan; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Delamar Flats site visit, June 2, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-104 - P-1987-108; Debbie Nolan; 106 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Latter Day Saints High Priest Picnic, picnic preparation, eating, campfire, and singing photos, June 10, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-109 - P-1987-110; Michael Luster; 62 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Mustang trap, Bishop Spring between Delamar and Rainbow Canyon, June 3, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-111; Debbie Nolan; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Rainbow Canyon petroglyphs (0-8); Rainbow Canyon (12-18); John Ballow's ranch (12-24), June 14, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-112; Debbie Nolan; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Rainbow Canyon; John Ballow's Ranch, May 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-113; Debbie Nolan; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Ken Lee's Ranch, May 9, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-114 - P-1987-119; Michael Luster; 126 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - June Cox Ranch, Meadow Valley, June 5, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-120 - P-1987-124; Debbie Nolan; 135 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Cemetery markers in Lincoln County, June 6, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-125; Michael Luster; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Cemetery markers in Lincoln County (0-17); Jay Schofield and Llelwyn Wilkinson making music, June 6, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-126; Michael Luster; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Prospecting, June 2, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-127; Michael Luster; 21 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Tungsten mine, June 4, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-128; Michael Luster; 21 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Bristol silver mine, May 5, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-129; Michael Luster; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Pierson Ranch, Camp Valley - ranch in Northern Lincoln County, with Jimmy Burris, ranch hand, May 17, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-130 - P-1987-131; Michael Luster; 36 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Carvings made by shepherds, cowboys in quaking aspens, June 18, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-132; Michael Luster; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Trail ride with guide Phil Truesdale (hunting guide), shepherds cabin, June 18, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-133; Michael Luster; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Carvings made by shepherds, cowboys in quaking aspens, June 18, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-134; Michael Luster; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Trail ride with guide Phil Truesdale (hunting guide), carvings made by shepherds, cowboys in quaking aspens (1-17); Vernacular architecture at Pony Springs (18-22); at Caliente (23-25), June 18, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-135; Michael Luster; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Coke ovens at Bristol Wells, June 16, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-136; Michael Luster; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Gordon Lytle's ranch (0-10); Jerry Hughes site visit (11-14); coke ovens (23-25), June 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-137; Michael Luster; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - [Ranching], May 19, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-138; Michael Luster; 28 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Basque Monument (1-5); Panaca cemetery (6-9); Frank Ernst site visit (10-24), May 11, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-139; Michael Luster; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - [Architecture; Ranching; Mining], June 16, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-140; Michael Luster; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - [Ranching], May 14, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-141 - P-1987-142; Michael Luster; 44 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - George Arnold plays music at home, with picture of himself and wife outside his trailer, May 19, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-143; Michael Luster; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Caliente Homecoming: Memorial Day celebration, May 22, 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-144 - P-1987-147; Michael Luster; 126 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Dutch ovens (0-8); Delmue Ranch (9-23), August 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-148; Blanton Owen; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Delmue Ranch, August 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-149 - P-1987-150; Blanton Owen; 44 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Dutch oven cooking, August 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-151; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Lincoln County monument (7-13); Dutch oven cooking (14-25), August 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-152; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - [Art; Food preparation; Ranching], August 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-153; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Delmue ranch and family photos, August 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-154 - P-1987-156; Blanton Owen; 73 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Vernacular architecture near Ione (2-16); In a High and Glorious Place folklife exhibit (17-24), September 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-157; Andrea Graham; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - [Vernacular architecture], September 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-158; Andrea Graham; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - [Lincoln County Folklife exhibit], September 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-159; Blanton Owen; 21 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - [Photo of Big Picture being taken], September 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-160; Blanton Owen; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - [Vernacular architecture], September 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-161 - P-1987-162; Andrea Graham; 47 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Mosquito Ranch; Monitor Ranch, September 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-163; Andrea Graham; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Stone, mud, railroad tie, and frame architecture at Stone House Ranch (0-16); at Mosquito Ranch (17-25), September 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-164; Andrea Graham; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Delmue Ranch (1-9); Gridley Days Fiddle context (16-19), June 1987, AFC 2017/002: P-1987-165; Blanton Owen; 19 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Silver Creek Ranch site visit, April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-001; Andrea Graham; 20 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Old photos from Doc Allen, April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-002; Blanton Owen; 22 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Copy photos, April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-003; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - John Kincheloe site visit (1-7); Stokes Castle (8-13); Easter Egg Hunt (14-23), April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-004; Blanton Owen; 23 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Lake Ranch (1-22); Allen Ranch (16-21); University of Nevada, Reno Ranch (16-21); Cortez (22-25), April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-005; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Cortez (1-10); Cortez Canyon (11-14); Vernacular architecture in Austin (18-24), April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-006; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Vernacular architecture in Austin (1-14); Austin Cemetery (15-24), April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-007; Andrea Graham; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Austin (1-11); Dry Creek Ranch (14-16); Ackerman Ranch (17-23); Battle Mountain (24-25), April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-008; Blanton Owen; 25 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Battle Mountain Cemetery (0-14), April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-009; Andrea Graham; 17 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Doyle and Beulah Davis - Doyle is a fiddle and guitar player; Beulah is the daughter of fiddler Eck Robertson (0-21); Battle Mountain (0-24), April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-010; Andrea Graham; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Battle Mountain (1); Lander Ranch (2-5); Home Ranch (6-24), April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-011; Blanton Owen; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Chuck Bispo at Austin (1-5); Dry Creek Ranch with Chuck Bispo, Bob Eddy and Benny Damele (6-24), March 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-012; Andrea Graham; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Dry Creek Ranch, March 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-013; Andrea Graham; 24 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Ackerman Ranch (1-16); Daniels Hay Ranch (19-22), April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-014; Blanton Owen; 22 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)
    - Accident with cow and semi (3-20); Dry Creek Ranch (21-22), April 1988, AFC 2017/002: P-1988-015; Blanton Owen; 22 black-and-white film negatives (35mm) (Box 7)